export default [
    {
      question: "RAM stands for?",
      choice1: "Read Access Memory",
      choice2: "Randomly Access Memory",
      choice3: "Random Access Memory",
      choice4: "Retains Access Memory",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following is not a Characteristic of Static RAM?",
      choice1: "Long life",
      choice2: "Faster",
      choice3: "Large size",
      choice4: "Low power consumption",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which is an extremely fast computer, which can execute hundreds of millions of instructions per second?",
      choice1: "Workstation",
      choice2: "Mini Computer",
      choice3: "Main Frame",
      choice4: "Supercomputer",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "PDAs are also called?",
      choice1: "PCs",
      choice2: "Laptops",
      choice3: "Tablets",
      choice4: "Handheld",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Keyboard also contains some special purpose keys such as Enter, Shift, Caps Lock, Num Lock, Space bar, Tab, and Print Screen is known as?",
      choice1: "Control keys",
      choice2: "Function Keys",
      choice3: "Special Purpose Keys",
      choice4: "None of the above",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question:
        " _____________ is an input device that is mostly used in notebook or laptop computer.",
      choice1: "Light Pen",
      choice2: "Track Ball",
      choice3: "Scanner",
      choice4: "Digitizer",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Name the device that converts text information into spoken sentences?",
      choice1: "Speech Sensors",
      choice2: "Speech Synthesizers",
      choice3: "Compact convertors",
      choice4: "Voice systems",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following Advantages of Dot Matrix Printer?",
      choice1: "Inexpensive",
      choice2: "Widely Used",
      choice3: "Other language characters can be printed",
      choice4: "All of the above",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "The memory is divided into large number of small parts called ?",
      choice1: "location",
      choice2: "cells",
      choice3: "rowsr",
      choice4: "columns",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following used to store data and instructions?",
      choice1: "CPU",
      choice2: "Mouse",
      choice3: "Memory",
      choice4: "Ports",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question:
        "NIC stands for?",
      choice1: "Network Internal Card",
      choice2: "Network Interconnect Card",
      choice3: "Network Interface Card",
      choice4: "Network Interface Component",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Debugging is the process of fixing a ______ in the software",
      choice1: "bug",
      choice2: "warning",
      choice3: "exception",
      choice4: "function",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Print debugging also called?",
      choice1: "Remote debugging",
      choice2: "Post-mortem debugging",
      choice3: "Tracing",
      choice4: "Static analysis",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "The terms bug and debugging are popularly attributed to Admiral Grace Hopper in the?",
      choice1: "1940",
      choice2: "1960",
      choice3: "1980",
      choice4: "995",
      answer: 1,
    },
  ];
  